Bimbopapirrin: PogChamp
Bimbopapirrin: Maybe Muted?
slovn1k: no sound bro
suurrend3r: no sound
suurrend3r: PogChamp PogChamp PogChamp
808kid: No audio
suurrend3r: yeah
Bimbopapirrin: We Good Bow'/
Marvi182: yes
suurrend3r: now it works
slovn1k: yeap it's on now
808kid: Yup
Bimbopapirrin: cheer5 Now its good
slovn1k: amazing
suurrend3r: Yeah use that please
quillford: sounded better with built in mic but still fine
coProof: Noooo I can’t right now
myaocat: hello geohot
twitchistrash788: Yo
coProof: What are you doing
myaocat: its geohot and those who dont know I'm getting sue by sony. (dj sound)
coProof: Okay bye I gotta go hang w a girl
ronaldlangeveld: good to see a python coder :D
barin122: lol
barin122: whats your keyboard, it sounds freaking amazing
myaocat: lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE
Zealeigh: What seekrit? I missed it? Kappa
aresfour: geohot I love seing you hacking
barin122: Hard to tell the name, looks even better than it sounds though
suurrend3r: essskettiiitt
Marvi182: das keyboard?
myaocat: keyboard for real hackers
twitchistrash788: Be careful using Spotify, accounts get leaked everyday
suurrend3r: LUL
Bryanswagbeast: Hello World!
Bryanswagbeast: mrmuff21 DrinkPurple
myaocat: how something from random is secret?
OPHaru: OMEGALUL
twitchistrash788: Lmao wtf
slimydude: lmfao
suurrend3r: lmaaaaoo
twitchistrash788: This is the state of the modern media
myaocat: now rap about bch!! 😎
memoryleak: lmao
OPHaru: thanks geohot, i am going to moon with my bch now
Bryanswagbeast: Fuck Politics
myaocat: lupoGG lupoGG lupoGG lupoGG lupoGG lupoGG lupoGG
twitchistrash788: The media in general has gone to shit
twitchistrash788: just sensationalism
myaocat: lupoTHINK
thecameroncobb: Please live stream more
Bryanswagbeast: Can someone help me with something regarding my laptop?
thecameroncobb: @Bryanswagbeast whats up?
myaocat: @tomcr00s3 how did you sent money without balance in your previous stream?
Marvi182: das keyboard? with black keycaps?
Bryanswagbeast: so i disassembled my laptopto replace the thermal paste and apparently i fucked up something that the display is blank now :(
Bryanswagbeast: sorry for autocorrect
myaocat: hahaahaha
myaocat: maybe it's time to change profile cash
thecameroncobb: @Bryanswagbeast like... your screen won't display anything?
myaocat: i have etherum. do you want eth?
Bryanswagbeast: yup but the led on the caps is still on
j4m3s_b0nd: which keyboard is that?
j4m3s_b0nd: model?
twitchistrash788: All I have is BAT lol
Bryanswagbeast: and the logo hp on the back is still on
Marvi182: i think thats a das keyboard
OPHaru: SELLOUT
myaocat: @tomcr00s3 i dont really have money and stop ignoring me. do you want eth?
thecameroncobb: @Bryanswagbeast you might have damaged the ribbon cable leading to the screen. I would recommend that you check that and disconnect and reconnect the ribbon cable
slimydude: do eet
Bryanswagbeast: alright thanks ill give it a try
twitchistrash788: Yeah they send free BAT periodically
twitchistrash788: But it's mostly useless for now
Bryanswagbeast: well i did disassembled it carefully
myaocat: open your wallets people
Bryanswagbeast: hey geo can yoy please send me money so i can buy a new laptop? @tomcr00s3
myaocat: lupoLONK
Bryanswagbeast: lmao
thecameroncobb: I don't have any crypto rn. If someone tells me where I can buy some and send it instantly I'll do it
myaocat: i send you eth cause fees on binance is shit
blackburn1911: hi people
blackburn1911: !uptime
myaocat: @thecameroncobb from private people or exchanges
barin122: drive your self driving car dude
barin122: who needs to run when you can be a gangsta in the self driving car lol
barin122: fair enough
thecameroncobb: @tomcr00s3 why aren't you on Instagram?
myaocat: or twitter
myaocat: if media talks about you it means you are worthy
twitchistrash788: Zuck
suurrend3r: Facebook
thecameroncobb: facebook
suurrend3r: Zuck = Facebook, Instagram, WhatsApp o.O
myaocat: that was fast transaction
thecameroncobb: You should go running...
myaocat: with btc you need to pay a lot money for transaction
twitchistrash788: lmfao
thecameroncobb: lmaooooo
magarky: hahahah
suurrend3r: LUL
magarky: LUL
un3okapi: LUL
igorovich: bring em down
blackburn1911: @tomcr00s3 how you learned about AI?
myaocat: lupoPOGGERS lupoPOGGERS
un3okapi: Yes.
kPrimal: a l e x j o n e s
thecameroncobb: Alex Jones
un3okapi: you're fine. :/
myaocat: oh no
xEHLE_: no, but he will appear behind you
myaocat: dont
kPrimal: alex jones alex jones alex jones
myaocat: lol
myaocat: america is after you now
OPHaru: don't refresh guys, stream offline forsenS
thecameroncobb: You should implement text-to-speech on your streams
myaocat: lupoPLS lupoPLS
memoryleak: Kappa
fwef64: @tomcr00s3 back to using google chrome I see
un3okapi: it's online Kappa
Captainmontereyjack: hobbTos hobbTos hobbTos
magarky: Jebaited
deep_40k: Play the piano behind you
myaocat: lupoWIFE lupoWIFE lupoWIFE lupoWIFE lupoWIFE
OPHaru: LUL
twitchistrash788: You gotta use FireFox
twitchistrash788: Way faster and leaner
twitchistrash788: plus it's built using Rust
barin122: Chrome is faster than Firefox on mac though
un3okapi: use brave :^)
thecameroncobb: Tor >;)
twitchistrash788: Chrome crashes and lags when I launch it
twitchistrash788: I use Brave occasionally
thecameroncobb: Tor browser ftw >:)
twitchistrash788: Yep Tor=Firefox security privacy
un3okapi: illegal fire arms drugs cp
thecameroncobb: @un3okapi true
twitchistrash788: lmao
jurodiwy_777: LUL
un3okapi: Can someone steal the money this time?
G07syvk9: sorry im poor
Madscars: what car you drive?
kPrimal: lamborghini tractor
blackburn1911: alias money="subscribe tomcr00s3"
cybermajestic: no sound
cIafran: @cybermajestic fine for me
vtcN_: that mouse scroll wheel sounds like a g502
juniperus1976: @cybermajestic all fine..
un3okapi: @vtcN_ LUL
slimydude: KappaPride
kripp_lover: crypto chad
cybermajestic: geohot hello
vtcN_: un3okapi LUL i have the same mouse, so was familar
myaocat: crypto is future?
twitchistrash788: virgin
kPrimal: crypto virgin
Bimbopapirrin: pwnNB
fn_mad: Sup
twitchistrash788: physical money virgin
un3okapi: @vtcN_ good ear SeemsGood
darrenofsky: what is your opinion on vscode?
cybermajestic: why you use nickname toomcroose, you nickname is geohot
OPHaru: bitcoin cash is the real bitcoin SeemsGood
cybermajestic: ?
suurrend3r: when geohot says "I don't know man" it really means "hell no".
suurrend3r: LUL
cromize: would you recommend going to study computer security these days?
thecameroncobb: @cromize yes
cybermajestic: @tomcr00s3 you play game?
jurodiwy_777: Dota stream when?
cybermajestic: plays dota
KingKewpa: is what youre doing the same as what wallets do to send txs
cybermajestic: hackers 1995))))
alexlucas_: What mac do you use?
lolegendal: hello
blackburn1911: RitzMitz
un3okapi: Kappa /
delta__vee: o/
jurodiwy_777: 4Head /
OPHaru: i do :)
kimmilol: Kappa /
jurodiwy_777: 4Head /
twitchistrash788: lmao
twitchistrash788: Try Nim
twitchistrash788: Nim is like Python the Speed of C Macros of Lisp
MrSnoopDog: erlang
thecameroncobb: Write your next project in Scratch
slimydude: factor Kappa
jurodiwy_777: what time it is where you live?
blackburn1911: create your own language
FalconJet_: try solving interview questions as fast as you can
un3okapi: speedrun making you own OS 4Head
foxubu: What happened?
denim_lap: all the best man
thecameroncobb: See... I am trying to trade some of my TRON for some BCH in Binance right now but they are "undergoing system maintenance" -_-
gpucluster: i remember when i unlock iphone 2g with geohot hardware unlock method , good times
thecameroncobb: Geo should grow his hair long like it was when he made that iPhone video
twitchistrash788: VS Code is nice
un3okapi: jet brains is better :^)
VertXY: using Scratch the programming language? Kappa
twitchistrash788: I can barely run Jet Brains IDE
twitchistrash788: They're so heavy
un3okapi: true :^)
Tuchopi: imlauer se la come con frutas
suurrend3r: @Tuchopi LUL LUL
foxubu: so that the money gets stolen again? lol
suurrend3r: @Tuchopi only english papu
Tuchopi: @suurrend3r ñ
gpucluster: I heard, or he asked to send him money? If you want money you need start PUBG or DOTA)))
OPHaru: lol no^
suurrend3r: LUL
foxubu: Ordering food 1:40 AM? Lol
Tuchopi: @suurrend3r LMAO
suurrend3r: @Tuchopi hahahah
ziggyzergling: LUL
yagurastation: Molo! from UTC 2
blackburn1911: hack uber to get free food
denim_lap: :(
Tuchopi: Hack mcdonalds to get vegan burguer
denim_lap: geohot
FalconJet_: ask for light ice
twitchistrash788: wow
un3okapi: no wtf
twitchistrash788: SF prices
un3okapi: you crazy?
TucoBenedictoPacificoJMR: could you share your dotfiles pls?
Tuchopi: Hack ice and make it hot
blackburn1911: hack McDonalds to get healthy food
denim_lap: ok guys
vtcN_: i put my ice in the microwave when im thirsty
suurrend3r: @Tuchopi he is not doing any hacking now
Tuchopi: @suurrend3r he's doing imlauer se la come con frutas
OPHaru: hack bch for free crypto
suurrend3r: he is retired from hacking
un3okapi: @vtcN_ do you put water in the freezer when you're hungry? 8^)
gpucluster: How much is his elo rating?'
TucoBenedictoPacificoJMR: over 9000
akalioceania: How much adderall did you take today lad?
gpucluster: nope , i see game in youtube / maybe 900))
FalconJet_: tim allen?
Tuchopi: tonald drump
thecameroncobb: Grow out your hair Geo
vtcN_: on your teeth
MessageOSRS: I like u :)
Tuchopi: he has been hacked away from reality
notbigd: scam
suurrend3r: hotz, politics is for losers?
thecameroncobb: Geo weren't you going to go for a run?
OPHaru: imagine delivering uber eats and u see geohotz PogChamp
Tuchopi: "Hello, i want to order a McHack with fritatas"
un3okapi: D:
foxubu: Lol
thecameroncobb: bruh
OPHaru: lmao
TheHandSolo: what the actual heck
OPHaru: i hacked ur order :)
vtcN_: re-order and hope it's the same guy
foxubu: When George freaks out :D
foxubu: Cute as hell lol
OPHaru: true
un3okapi: true
kishan0505: Whats up man
Tuchopi: Hack them and put 100 orders by random names and random places
kishan0505: !uptime
suurrend3r: there's no bot
kishan0505: Oh ok
Tuchopi: !hack
kishan0505: What ide does he use?
LuminousCS: vim
kishan0505: Ok thanks man
TheHandSolo: so if he keeps up these stream numbers he will be able to get partner on twitch with out even trying
TheHandSolo: nah your only affiliate. its the 1st step to partnered
TheHandSolo: u havent got the "tick" next to your name
myaocat: why don't you put yourself in science & technology category? you will get more views too
TheHandSolo: 1000% agree
myaocat: c&p stack overflow
myaocat: @tomcr00s3 not sure how but if you will be in science & technology you will be 1st there
gucci_uzi: cheer10 coding sucks to learn
roosterhax: its kinda complex doing a crypto transaction, the really hax way, thats why it shouldn't be suckie
myaocat: why is it printing 2 ip address?
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 bro pls dont fall on my face
myaocat: i wish i could pay subs with etherium because fee is only 0.01eth
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 evrybody doing bitcoin
newtomcroose: yu
newtomcroose: Hello
suurrend3r: This is hard af
myaocat: ezpz
newtomcroose: hello
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 hello my name is jeff
insaeq: @newtomcroose kamikaze quotes :0
jeromez: what is your tmux prefix
insaeq: dlxxF
newtomcroose: My name is jeff . please call me jeff
newtomcroose: George doing bitcoin
newtomcroose: that's how much we have in common
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 lets talk about love
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 in the summer night
newtomcroose: george have grammy awards ?
newtomcroose: george do u have grammy awards ?
myaocat: don't you add newline when doing write?
newtomcroose: https://www.twitch.tv/tomcr00s3
newtomcroose: comma.ai/shop
fengyuhen: (´｡• ᵕ •｡`) ♡
myaocat: lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoGG lupoGG lupoGG lupoGG lupoGG
suurrend3r: @newtomcroose I think he muted you :(
newtomcroose: politics is the mind killer
myaocat: he probably muted me too lol
ssh4422: the audio dosent work on smartphone
newtomcroose: he muted everybody , even elon musk direct message in twitter :|
myaocat: lupoYE
maruchandayo: !uptime
newtomcroose: !no
newtomcroose: give me some rice
newtomcroose: i need RICE
TheHandSolo: i think he should code a bot for his chat
suurrend3r: @Tuchopi are you still here?
newtomcroose: now you get too much to lose
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 can u fight with khabib nurmagomedov ?
PlayITAntabuzz: hrllo
PlayITAntabuzz: how are you?
myaocat: fine and you?
PlayITAntabuzz: good thank you
myaocat: np lupoYE lupoYE
egohot: Bug bounty ???
h4v0k22: Have you tried debugging using something like btcdeb? https://github.com/kallewoof/btcdeb
myaocat: lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE lupoHYPE
BrainIet: ClappyHype
clinuco: DoritosChip DoritosChip
newtomcroose: nooo
newtomcroose: are u kidding me ?
newtomcroose: thats not gonna work now
myaocat: shh
Bryanswagbeast: Eh! Im back!
Bryanswagbeast: what is tmux? is it for windows as well?
Bryanswagbeast: i think hash is part of the bitcoin
myaocat: why do you have star
Bryanswagbeast: im a subscriber
Bryanswagbeast: ninjaCreep mthGrin
myaocat: lupoHEY lupoHEY lupoHEY
Caene: So you're going by "tomcr00s3" now nerd? Haha whats up douche bag, it's Tanner from Highschool. Remember me? Me and the guys used to give you a hard time in school. Sorry you were just an easy target lol. I can see not much has changed. Remember Sarah the girl you had a crush on? Yeah we're married now. I make over 200k a year and drive a mustang GT. I guess some things never change huh loser? Nice catching up lol. Pathetic..
myaocat: nice
BrainIet: PartyTime
myaocat: if i had money i would subs to ninja too
myaocat: lupoNICE lupoNERD
myaocat: lupoCRY lupoCRY lupoCRY lupoCRY
Bryanswagbeast: Caene hes making money everywhere wdym? your the loser lmao!
myaocat: it's fake comment
myaocat: if he came here he is the loser lupoTHINK
karlitios: Lol Caene. Probably troll. If not, you're the one who's pathetic.
Caene: People actually getting baited by copy pasta LUL
Caene: I thought it was a myth
Bryanswagbeast: you dumb loser lol
Caene: LUL
myaocat: so did you fuck sarah?
Caene: ^
Caene: <3
myaocat: lupoCRINGE lupoCREEP
Caene: sarah turned out being a transgender, so she fucked me in the ass
Bryanswagbeast: Yo geohot hash is what makes up a bitcoin
suurrend3r: Go hotz go, never give up never surrender
PlayITAntabuzz: its the rats
h4v0k22: Mind dumping the raw tx hex in the chat?
maruchandayo: i wonder what the heck is going on inside of hes head.
maruchandayo: he type too fast...
newtomcroose: no i get too much to lose
Bryanswagbeast: mthSip
myaocat: its just the keyboard is loud and mouse lupoNINJA
Bryanswagbeast: so satisfying
PlayITAntabuzz: apm king
newtomcroose: fucking advertising in twitch :|
Bryanswagbeast: thats the reason why im getting a blackwidow chroma version 2 from Razer
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 who need a hero ?
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 bro . how u can eat 2 breakfast ?
Bryanswagbeast: Hey geo use try and catch to see where it stops running the code! @tomcr00s3
egohot: try and except
Caene: he burns 40000 calories a minute just by using his brain, so two breakfasts seems reasonable.
Bryanswagbeast: lol except
myaocat: did he write all of that?
Bryanswagbeast: yeah
myaocat: so why it doesn't run lol
RishabhDeepSingh: Heyyyyyy
Bryanswagbeast: people proud when they type blablabla words a minute when he codes a full page under 1 minutw
Hrudu: @tomcr00s3 sup bruh Keepo
PlayITAntabuzz: simple is beter
PlayITAntabuzz: go eter
Bryanswagbeast: Try and Except!
newtomcroose: @tomcr00s3 if u wanna do a challenge . solve this https://projecteuler.net/problem=600
myaocat: R)
RishabhDeepSingh: What are we building?
myaocat: ps4 exploit
ssh4422: @newtomcroose this is too easy
newtomcroose: @ssh4422 its easy for u . not for geohot SwiftRage
Bryanswagbeast: he is building his own bitcoin transaction
RishabhDeepSingh: ok thanks @Bryanswagbeast
newtomcroose: @RishabhDeepSingh u r so nob
RishabhDeepSingh: yes i am :(
ekxose1: @tomcr00s3 what do you think is true that very few people agree with you on?
newtomcroose: @ekxose1 what do u think about eating rice in mars ?
ekxose1: pretty lame
newtomcroose: noooooo
Bryanswagbeast: do any of you try Codingame?
Caene: codinggame?
RishabhDeepSingh: @Bryanswagbeast yes me
Bryanswagbeast: no Codingame
Bryanswagbeast: hey should try to solve as much puzzle within a certain time
Bryanswagbeast: meant he
myaocat: 3:33 AM
Bryanswagbeast: where does he live?
myaocat: merica
Hrudu: @tomcr00s3 do you intercat with chat sir ? Keepo
th3_maj0r: yo boys
Bryanswagbeast: lets all start a project!
Bryanswagbeast: lets hack the ps4 and xbox one s
myaocat: no
ekxose1: cryptodoggies!
Hrudu: who's on java / kotlin / android bois ? Keepo i wanna make a friend
myaocat: lupoSPOOK lupoSPOOK
Bryanswagbeast: @hrudu wdym
myaocat: @bryanswagbeast can you pon pon smiley here? lupoSHARK
Hrudu: @tomcr00s3 Geohot interact with chat BabyRage
Hrudu: @Bryanswagbeast are u an IT guy ? Keepo
RishabhDeepSingh: @Hrudu me
Hrudu: @RishabhDeepSingh we can be friends and talk Keepo
RishabhDeepSingh: Yes sure mate
myaocat: kotlin going to replace java for android
RishabhDeepSingh: it has already replaced
myaocat: same as swift for objective c
Bryanswagbeast: ninjaPon
Hrudu: not quite sure tho Keepo
myaocat: everything is dying fast
ekxose1: @tomcr00s3 thoughts on curing aging?
Hrudu: did u guys hear about java 11 prices and stuff ? Keepo
myaocat: no
Hrudu: oracle is FCKED
myaocat: how
Bryanswagbeast: hey guys should i buy the rtx 2070?
RishabhDeepSingh: Nope
myaocat: oracle sue google for using java lol
Hrudu: java 11 will not be free Keepo
myaocat: java is shit
Hrudu: taxeable by proc Keepo
Bryanswagbeast: no rtx 2070?
Hrudu: @tomcr00s3 geohot would u mind interact with ur viewers ? Keepo
Bryanswagbeast: hes busy right now
Hrudu: yea
myaocat: he is working
Bryanswagbeast: mthPose
myaocat: lupoTRIG
Bryanswagbeast: mthOMEGA
myaocat: lupoRAGE
Hrudu: is that python btw ?
PlayITAntabuzz: hex
Bryanswagbeast: yes Python 3
PlayITAntabuzz: he program in hex
Hrudu: ok
myaocat: assembly
Hrudu: actually started from scratch ? XD
Bryanswagbeast: yup
Hrudu: lordy Keepo
Bryanswagbeast: this is the second stream
myaocat: lupoNERD
Hrudu: ok
PlayITAntabuzz: something different to my "hello world" script
Bryanswagbeast: his first stream is already uploaded on YouTube
Hrudu: @PlayITAntabuzz 4Head
Hrudu: i'll check it out
PlayITAntabuzz: @Hrudu :)
Bryanswagbeast: print("Hello")
PlayITAntabuzz: help print
Hrudu: never digged in python tbh Keepo
Hrudu: as i dont know its advantages and stuff , need knowledge girls BabyRage
PlayITAntabuzz: is it fast is it greasy?
PlayITAntabuzz: i prefer fortran
Bryanswagbeast: Python can be confusing
Hrudu: isnt powerfull tho ? Keepo
PlayITAntabuzz: :D
Bryanswagbeast: it requires good indentation unlike java
Bryanswagbeast: python is powerful
PlayITAntabuzz: no parser lol
Bryanswagbeast: good for automating stuff and hacking as well!
Hrudu: yea i heard so
Bryanswagbeast: i like java better
Hrudu: u on java bryan ?
Bryanswagbeast: yeah
Hrudu: nice
PlayITAntabuzz: rly pepehands
Hrudu: wich area ? Keepo
PlayITAntabuzz: show us the grease tom
saulgd: does Geo only use python?
Bryanswagbeast: Try and Except @tomcr00s3
Hrudu: he's a python expert seems like Keepo
Hrudu: @Bryanswagbeast wich area bryan Keepo
Bryanswagbeast: California
Hrudu: not the location , which area you use java in ?
Hrudu: platform
PlayITAntabuzz: will i be same as him with same keyboard
PlayITAntabuzz: i will maybe buy today
Hrudu: web dev , mobile ? ....
Bryanswagbeast: wtf then be specific
PlayITAntabuzz: also i will try buy some friends
Hrudu: mb Keepo
Bryanswagbeast: pc
Hrudu: desktop app ?
Bryanswagbeast: for java?
Hrudu: yea
Bryanswagbeast: whichever
Bryanswagbeast: mostly for games
PlayITAntabuzz: 1 forward 2 backward
Hrudu: ok
Bryanswagbeast: and c for games as well
PlayITAntabuzz: show us where the trouble is bob
PlayITAntabuzz: put some grease on it
PlayITAntabuzz: alittle ducktape coding
mr08040: Good morning from the East Coast
Bryanswagbeast: Good Night from the West Side
mr08040: Seriously
PlayITAntabuzz: sqeeze the hex out of it
bensiso18: Sabbat Shalom form Israel
PlayITAntabuzz: shalom sabbat
ekxose1: @tomcr00s3 thoughts on neuralink? and invasive BCI's in general?
BigGucciGuap: HeyGuys
PlayITAntabuzz: !sr gucci gang
BigGucciGuap: PartyTime what it do ladies
clinuco: FutureMan
Bimbopapirrin: pwnPG
PlayITAntabuzz: lizard
BigGucciGuap: lizard squad on your forehead
mr08040: while true; do clear; ./tx.py; sleep 1; done
PlayITAntabuzz: LIZARD SQUAD
suurrend3r: @ekxose1 he is 100% focused on the code
PlayITAntabuzz: no focus on chat pepe
ekxose1: i got a bank of questions so hopefully he'll do a quick q&a
PlayITAntabuzz: @ekxose1 he use razer
Hrudu: sup bruhs Keepo
PlayITAntabuzz: :(
h4v0k22: not sure if this helps, running bitcoin-cli decoderawtransaction https://pastebin.com/nLiwcZ4T
h4v0k22: debugging the scriptsig suggests there's a problem
h4v0k22: 473044022065d0457d1494fa732af57b32301c7e5ada768da835bf2b7d5c960c47bb21ff2602204a8707d8f27a876b52e1a5c013fc461ae521d995601ee2499b66a81762eaafd741210256fa29513e4c252be196b12642ff678022b8992d08c3a9d8cf1cd6d9313b566d
PlayITAntabuzz: were being screwed by the damn rats again
PlayITAntabuzz: 3k
greis795: do you work in a company?
egohot: where's your monte ?
Nagato_Pain: is that java script or python guts @tomcr00s3
Nagato_Pain: guys*
greis795: python i think
keepingtrckofthisacct: its python
theGeekPirate: ^
h4v0k22: I've tried running the script sig through btcdeb, this usually creates a stack debugger
greis795: but he also types in command line bash
h4v0k22: Trying to see if this is not caused by the difference between btc and bch, but the script sig should work find
Nagato_Pain: @greis795 @keepingtrckofthisacct thanks
h4v0k22: btcdeb 473044022065d0457d1494fa732af57b32301c7e5ada768da835bf2b7d5c960c47bb21ff2602204a8707d8f27a876b52e1a5c013fc461ae521d995601ee2499b66a81762eaafd741210256fa29513e4c252be196b12642ff678022b8992d08c3a9d8cf1cd6d9313b566d
h4v0k22: also, nice alterantive to bitcoinjs-lib is bcoin :D
h4v0k22: full bch support
h4v0k22: bcoin.io
Nagato_Pain: @tomcr00s3 keyboard that u use ??
h4v0k22: https://github.com/bcoin-org/bcash
bool3max: have you ever considered using a tiling window manager or something
bool3max: all those floating browser windows are a pain
th3_maj0r: he is on mac
blackburn1911: yeeey
memoryleak: Pog
PlayITAntabuzz: POG
h4v0k22: Well done :D
Bimbopapirrin: PogChamp
greis795: boom
slimydude: VoHiYo
un3okapi: Pog
un3okapi: Holy shit
Bimbopapirrin: HYPE
greis795: boom bitch!
PlayITAntabuzz: YOU ARE BITCOIN
Caene: u r bitcoin
slimydude: can you explain the problem again? i was looking at another window.
clyde542: "What ever you're having, I want some"
h4v0k22: So now do it on the real bitcoin, not on bitcoin cash
th3_maj0r: wooow
DREKANworld: I don't hear anything is it normal guys ?
th3_maj0r: nope
Bimbopapirrin: LUL i have no bitcoin :(
Bimbopapirrin: pwnMIR2
tomcr00s3: bitcoincash:qzgkpum2asc2frhzj9n9hsy9sq233xrqhys5p05c8k
magarky: 10 cents PogChamp
h4v0k22: congrats
PlayITAntabuzz: LOL
ashimathilda: you are beast bro
chaprio1: #ad Kappa Kappa
GoldenDickies: bch is bitcoin
PlayITAntabuzz: lol
h4v0k22: can use the regtest network too :) don't always deploy, but when you do, it's in production
th3_maj0r: is that an iphone?
GoldenDickies: 1 sat fee
Nagato_Pain: your keyboard Hyper X ?
soad188: JUST DO IT
Bimbopapirrin: CiGrip
Bimbopapirrin: Lets do it bois
slimydude: LMAO
un3okapi: LOOOOOOOL
DasMastah: Wow lol
twintowerpower: He definitely regrets all of this
twintowerpower: just trying to keep up apperances for his loyal viewers :D
Nagato_Pain: Hyper X keyboard ? ?
Nagato_Pain: @tomcr00s3
un3okapi: just hack time 4Head
blackburn1911: LUL
potimotti: ma boy hotz live <3
soad188: LUL
th3_maj0r: ahahahahah
un3okapi: D:
blackburn1911: at least it worked for 1m
suurrend3r: omg
suurrend3r: this is just amazing
h4v0k22: OP_RETURN
greis795: can i ask something that i dont undersand?why programmers prefer running python from command line?
h4v0k22: What should we use in the ./seekrit ? this just random data?
un3okapi: Geohot - "bitcoin sucks"
un3okapi: got the headline.
un3okapi: thanks
h4v0k22: burning coins doing that
keepingtrckofthisacct: @greis795 please clarify? python is a language accessible from the command line.
z0di4ckx: hi
keepingtrckofthisacct: @greis795 he's coding in 'vi' but executing via the cmdline
greis795: @keepingtrckofthisacct why not use jupyter or a text editor and instead run python from command line which is not very user friendly?
twintowerpower: he is using a text editor
keepingtrckofthisacct: @greis795 he 'is' using an editor, just not a 'grapical' one
greis795: oh ok
potimotti: its vim
greis795: sorry for my noob questions
potimotti: its fine. i dont even know vim myself. heared its difficut to get started with
keepingtrckofthisacct: @greis795 don't apologize. you're learning
h4v0k22: yeah, no rbf in csh
unDe4dman: 1
greis795: i learn data science now and i am not fully familiar with all the concepts
greis795: @keepingtrckofthisacct thx man!
keepingtrckofthisacct: @greis795 then, you'll become good friends with python!
juniperus1976: Me
greis795: yeah!
greis795: vim is like bash?
Bimbopapirrin: PogChamp me :)
keepingtrckofthisacct: @gr
keepingtrckofthisacct: @greis795 no, vim is an editor, bash is an environment
juniperus1976: nerve-racking
greis795: so vim i guess is a special text editor that u can use in bash?
keepingtrckofthisacct: @greis795 ...zsh,csh,bash, etc
paradox109: @greis795 just google vim editor
Number___Nine: yo
twintowerpower: we may need emergency surgery in the studio...
keepingtrckofthisacct: @greis795 'bash' is 'how' you interact with the system
paradox109: nitial release:2 November 1991(26 years ago) thats vim for you
ququa111: i dont understand coding but im watchin u
paradox109: lol
markoancev123: why am i watching this i dont know jack shit about programming LUL
un3okapi: you watch him for his political commentary
h4v0k22: use OP_RETURN
markoancev123: must be
Number___Nine: >4:34 am lol
mrgh0st0: its satisfying :D
markoancev123: 1:34 pm here
Number___Nine: 12:34 here
suurrend3r: 08:35 am here
greis795: 14:35 here
soad188: mostly european are seiing this
juniperus1976: 13:35
h4v0k22: Just append am output with OP_RETURN data so you can write data to the chain
z0di4ckx: 7:35 am hare
return100000001: hellooo
markoancev123: i dont know anything about programming what language should i start with
paradox109: english
soad188: @markoancev123 c, is really easy
juicegohard: python
paradox109: LuL
ququa111: what about python?
Number___Nine: @markoancev123 python
h4v0k22: OP_RETURN will not be spendable, but your other output with the value will, the OP_RETURn output doesn't need a value
z0di4ckx: he use Python
markoancev123: python i dont want a snake Kappa
juicegohard: ZzzzZzzz
keepingtrckofthisacct: the 'pythons' have it
z0di4ckx: python 3
soad188: c is easy to understand for people that starts programming
soad188: but useless today
paradox109: learn autoit for botting lol
Number___Nine: @soad188 yeah, and then you hit the memory model and concurency, lol
h4v0k22: Keep your existing output, and just add another with an OP_RETURN script and a 0 value output
juniperus1976: language does not matter.
paradox109: @juniperus1976 then write in machine code smartass
paradox109: lol
juniperus1976: I do it every day... ;-)
ququa111: 4Head
keepingtrckofthisacct: @paradox109 prolly not what @juniperus1976 meant. picking any specific lang isn't going to 'make' you a programmer.
h4v0k22: Keep your existing output, and just add another with an OP_RETURN script and a 0 value output, OP_RETURN outputs are not meant to be spent, and are prunable
h4v0k22: istandard yes
Number___Nine: why is geohot sitting on his old crappy chair?
h4v0k22: these prevent some unwanted tx types
h4v0k22: yes
a28b: hello
h4v0k22: No no, real bitcoin, we heard it hear
th3_maj0r: "fake"
mrgh0st0: @Number___Nine clever enough to not buy fancy chairs
Number___Nine: mrgh0st0 but he did buy a while ago, iirc
h4v0k22: You could also try a vanity address for what you're attempting to do
h4v0k22: https://bitcoin.stackexchange.com/questions/20305/what-is-vanity-address
ragemaster999: here we go
mrgh0st0: @Number___Nine maybe he broke it when another celebration :D
ququa111: LUL
a28b: LUL
h4v0k22: OP_RETURN is limited to 40 bytes of data
unDe4dman: LUL
greis795: hahaha
a28b: LUL LUL
Lythaslol: why is he doing in on bitcoin cash and not bitcoin?
greis795: !uptime
a28b: PogChamp
juniperus1976: Yeah
ququa111: POGGERS
tomcr00s3: https://explorer.bitcoin.com/bch/tx/f5db7ccb0fc0a64cbbaab00e1ba98f12d7629f12db9086eadbe66170413241b2
greis795: how many hours did it take?
markoancev123: how big is your head?
un3okapi: what happened to boba tea?
th3_maj0r: ahahahaah
Number___Nine: how about the chair? lol
magarky: How big is your penis
rrdpc: 15 hours
h4v0k22: good technical coding session, pity it's BCH and not BTC ¯(°_o)/¯. ¯_(ツ)_/¯
ququa111: i just wanna suck ur ballz
th3_maj0r: How much long is the cable of ur keyboard?
XPicolasCageX: Okay, stupid question.. can you update your dotfiles rep in github?
a28b: LUL
Ropat: When did you start playing piano?
Lythaslol: @tomcr00s3 do you prefer BCH over BTC?
th3_maj0r: hahahahaha
un3okapi: how much can you bench?
clyde542: Do you still blaze george?
Ropat: Thanks!
XPicolasCageX: Best way to start learning python?
cromize: would you go studying computer sec. these days?
juicegohard: LOL Fedcoin
markoancev123: can you hack me a pornhub account
unDe4dman: AHAHAHAHAHAHAAHHAAH
a28b: LUL
clyde542: I love you being as human as possible, keep it up!
suurrend3r: do you like Freebsd?
egohot: have you ever used vpn
mrgh0st0: whats your next goal on comma ai ?
ququa111: delicious orgasm Kreygasm
Quiplash: adderall or ritalin
h4v0k22: When we doing some lightning hacking?
un3okapi: trump or hillary?
XPicolasCageX: @tomcr00s3 Any reason you are not using any plugins for vim?
h4v0k22: sending ln tx's using pythong
h4v0k22: python*
egohot: does tomcr00s3 ever used vpn
willoregan: any ideas for next Twitch session?
un3okapi: that was fun!
willoregan: yep, that was cool
Lythaslol: @tomcr00s3 if you could recommend one book everyone should read as a programmer which one is it?
suurrend3r: you say that you read Linux, Windows and Mac kernel, what about BSD?
th3_maj0r: Try to stream more bro
Ropat: Do you take vacations and if so do you have a specific destination you want to travel to?
Number___Nine: read linux the whol 5M lines lol?
blackburn1911: were to learn AI and machine learning like you?
athmo2: vacations = scam, life is work people
juniperus1976: idea for next stream: reconstruct a 3d scene from photos with ml
Ropat: oh ok
un3okapi: they're advertisement's propaganda D:
Number___Nine: twitch checkers
egohot: did you used vpn in hacking days ?
th3_maj0r: Which is the plugin that u are using to block ads on firefox?
juniperus1976: hard fun! ;-)
cromize: live rap?
h4v0k22: lightning on bitcoin, do some hand crafting of hashed time lock contracts
un3okapi: code deepfake from ground up :)
ququa111: are u gonna upload this yt ?
willoregan: analyse instrumental audio file, generate flows and rhymes
h4v0k22: You can do using p2sh, more flexibility in having custom redeem scripts
h4v0k22: isStandard is very restrictive on output formats
greis795: where do u work?
alexlucas_: steam bots ?
un3okapi: @greis795 comma.ai
h4v0k22: used for multisig, and backwards compatability with segwit
greis795: @un3okapi thx
juniperus1976: ml is boring...? hmmm
h4v0k22: Also use for HTLC's
h4v0k22: yes , peter todd's challenges sha1 , sha256 etc
h4v0k22: https://lists.linuxfoundation.org/pipermail/bitcoin-dev/2013-September/003253.html
h4v0k22: Social scalability :D
h4v0k22: Hashed version of the bitcoin script used for unlocking the funds, logic is in the input instead of the output
h4v0k22: https://www.soroushjp.com/2014/12/20/bitcoin-multisig-the-hard-way-understanding-raw-multisignature-bitcoin-transactions/
h4v0k22: multisig is one of the first usecases for p2sh
h4v0k22: Yes!
h4v0k22: LN channels
h4v0k22: HTLC
h4v0k22: Atomic Swaps
MrPeppah: adios
un3okapi: gngn
juicegohard: pce pit
h4v0k22: Thanks for sharing the codeing session
juniperus1976: Bye
a28b: bye
juicegohard: pce out
Ropat: bye
greis795: bye
XiaoLongBao: bai
alexlucas_: bye
egohot: night
DasMastah: byebye
th3_maj0r: bb
memoryleak: bye